# MATHIS ALLEN

DEVELOPER

## **ABOUT ME**

I am passionate developer, as well as a dedicated athlete and competitor. I have a dynamic and curious personality with a strong team orientation gained through 15 years of competitve Horseball, and continuing as a coach and referee.

My foundation in competitive sports has served me well as I move into the developer world. I am constantly seeking opportunities for process improvement as I enhance my skills. I am comfortable traveling for work.

### CONTACT

06 78 98 32 77

mathis.allen.pro@gmail.com

5 rue du cornier, 34380, Saint-Martin-De-Londres. France

<u>www.mathis-allen.fr</u>

bit.ly/3RAruMB

## SKILLS

 JAVA
 • • • • •

 C#
 • • • •

 TypeScript
 • • • •

 Git
 • • • •

 SQL
 • • • •

Linux System • • • • •

Dart • • • •

DevOps Tools • • • • •

Cyber Tools • • • •

French • • • • •

English • • • •

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Crédit Agricole Technologies & Services -

FullStack Developer

SEPT 2021 - OCT 2024

I recently completed my work-study contract for Crédit Agricole Technologies & Services in Montpellier. As a member of the team "Security for CA-TS", I developed solutions for cyber-security within an agile context. My first assignment was participating in the development of the IAM (Identity Access Management) of CA-TS, which is a software package by Netwrix. I gained experience in .NET, Powershell, SQL and Netwrix's custom language. My second mission was the development, as a tech lead, of a solution which manages the company's vulnerabilities. My team and I developed it using Spring Boot (JAVA), Node and Angular (TS).

#### PriceComparator - DevOps Internship

JAN 2021 - FEB 2021

Within PriceComparator, an agile french start-up specializing in competitive intelligence, I developed some web scraping scripts using Javascript. Additionally, I implemented a REST API, using Play framework (Scala), to establish a connection between Prestashop e-shop and perform CRUD operations on products. Finally, I gained experience in DevOps by deploying this API using Jenkins CI/CD and Docker.

#### Various Challenges

JAN 2021 - TODAY

In a constant quest for new skills, I regularly participate in various technical contests. During one of these challenges, a full weekend hackathon organized by CA-GIP and Google Cloud Platform on the DevOps theme, I discovered Kubernetes. I also recently won a coding contest challenge for the interns of Crédit Agricole Technologies & Services which delved into Java.

Dealing with Cyber-Security, platforms as Root-me, HackTheBox, Ozint, and others are my companions. I continuously keep an eye on the subject.

# **EDUCATION**

EPSI - Montpellier - France

SEP 2022 - OCT 2024 (MASTER)

In <u>progress</u>: a "Computer Science and Exploitation System Expert" graduation, specializing in Cyber-Security.

**EPSI - Montpellier - France** 

2019 - 2022 (BACHELOR)

I graduated with an "Application Design Builder" Bachelor.